Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
- H
  - Harrison, Shelley A., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hartigan, Ellen F., circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hase, Leopold, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hastak, Makarand, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hauser, Norbert, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hausmann, Erich, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hayes, Christopher, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hebbert, C. Mark, circa 1955 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hechhouse, Phil, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Heckman, Leila, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Heinzelman, Fred, 1960, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Hellerstein, Lisa, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Henderson, Annette, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Henkel, Herbert L., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hennessey, Raymond G., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Henry, Otto, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Herbach, L., undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Herbst, Marc, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Herr, Barber, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Hertzberg, Constantine, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Hessel, Alexander, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Hewlett, William R., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Heyke, John E., Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Hibben, Samuel G., undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Hielscher, Andreas, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Hiller, Maruin H., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hinkaty, Charles J., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hinte, Fred, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Hirayama, Kozo, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Hoadley, George B., undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Hochman, Jack, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Hochstadt, Harry, 1964, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Hockney, Donald, 1979, 1982, 1986, circa 1996 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hoff, Nicholas J., 1953, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Hoffman, Harmon F., undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hoiberg, Svend, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Holloway, Helen, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Holub, Helen and Helene, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Holzmacher, Robert G., undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Homberger, Conrad, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hommer, Henry F., undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Honser, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hooper, John W., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hoover, Charles W., Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hora, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Horn, Paul, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Horton, Edward Everett, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Horton, Lishia, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Horvath, John S., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Horwitch, Mel, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Hostetter, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Hotzler, Russell K., undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Houlihan, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Houser, George G., undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Houston, Theodore Warren, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Howard, C. Douglas, undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Howley, Eamon, undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Huber, Robert E., undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hultin, Jerry MacArthur, undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Hummel, Susan Flynn, undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Hunt, Donald F., undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Huseland, Norman, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Hutter, Rudolf, undated (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hyman, Jocette, circa 1996 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Hynn, Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
- I
  - Iacono, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Iacono, Margie (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Iafrate, G., undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Iftekhar, Lamia, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Immergut, Edmund H., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Ingham, Joanne, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Ingram, Maxwell, undated (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Iorio, Jeffrey, undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Ip, Tak-Cheung, undated (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Irani, Ray R., undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Iskander, Magued, undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Ivanoff, Donald, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- J
  - Jacobs, Eddy, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Jacobs, Joseph J., 1936, 1975, 1978, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1986, 1990, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Jacobs, Linda, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Jacobs, Zena, undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Jahnke, Craig C., undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - James, Dorothy, undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Jansen, Albert F.W., undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Jansen, Colleen, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Janssen, Gimter, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Jazwinski, Arthur, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Jear, E., undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Jenkins, Carol, undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Jiang, Zhong-Ping, undated (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Johnson, Anthony, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Johnson, D.H., undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Johnson, I. Birger, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Jones, Barry, undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Jones, Francis T., undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Jonsson, Eric, undated (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Jordan, Peter, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Juran, Ilan, undated (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Jung, Check K., undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Juretschke, Hellmut J., undated (Box 4, Folder 129)
- K
  - Kabasakalian, Peter, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Kaczmarek, Richard F., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Kadik, Abdelhamid, undated (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Kahn, Alexander, undated (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Kahn, Herman (1922-1983), undated (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Kahn, Sophie, undated (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Kahne, Stephen, undated (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Kalil, James, undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Kalkhoran, Iraj M., undated (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Kalotay, Andrew, undated (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Kammen, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Kane, Jasper, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Kangas, Edward A., 2000 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Kapfer, (William H.), undated (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Kapila, Vikram, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Kaplan, David, undated (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Kaplan, Helene, undated (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Kaplan, Seymour, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Kappaz, Michael H., 2010 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Kappenburg, William, undated (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Karnaugh, Maurice, undated (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Karri, Ramesh, undated (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Kasper, Victor Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Kastarelos, Konstantinos, undated (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Katchalski (Katzir), Ephraim, 1973, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Katsaggelos, Aggelos K., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Katz, J. Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Katz, Larry W., undated (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Katzen, Raphael, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Kaufman, Harold, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Kaufman, Michael D., 1996 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Kavanagh, Thomas C., undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Keenan, A.J., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Kellogg, Brainerd, undated (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Kelly, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Kemp, L. Franklin, undated (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Kemper, Joseph, undated (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Kerge, Steve, undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Kerr, Michelle, undated (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Kershenbaum, Aaron, undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Kertesz, Dennis J., undated (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Keyworth, George A., undated (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Khaimchayev, Tamara, undated (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Khan, Eakalak, undated (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Khorrami, Farshad, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - King, Carolyn D., undated (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Kinsey, Henry R., undated (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Kirk, Raymond E., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Kjeldaas, Terje, undated (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Kleiner, Eugene, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Kline, Tom, undated (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Klosner, Jerome, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Knudson, John Immanuel, 1935, 1953, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Kobayakawa, Shinya, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kobayashi, Koji, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Ed, udnated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Koehler, George R., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Koeing, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Korfage, Willard, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Korman, Samuel, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Korniczky, Stephen S., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kossay, David, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kouar, Mohammed, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kozol, Lauren, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kramer (Kramer-Koehler), Pamela E., 1978, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kramer, William, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kreiling, Fred, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kremer, Richard H., undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kriftcher, Noel N., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kristol, Irving, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kubat, Joseph E., undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kuiken, Kathryn, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kumar, Sunil, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kunhardt, Erich, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kuo, Spencer P., 1995, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kurz, Ludwik, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kwartler, A., circa 1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kwei, T.K., undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
- L
  - Lago, James (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Lai, Jai-Lu L. (J.L.), undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - LaMarsh, John, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Lan, Chuan-Tan Edward, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Landis, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lando, Jerome, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Landau, Gad. M., undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Lane, "Coach", 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Lane, V. Hugo, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lannon, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Larkin, Michael, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lassen, Walter C., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Laster, Richard, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - LaTourette, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Lauren, Sidney, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Lawson, Richard, circa 1937 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lederman, Peter, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lee, Bernard S., undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lee, C., undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Lee, David M., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Lee, Marvin, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Leeb, Leonard, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Lehman, Sheila, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Leiber, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Leistner, William E, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - LeKashman, John Q., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Lemelson, Jerome H., 1995, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Lender, Samuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Lengyel, Emil, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Lentz, Robert H., undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Leonard, Martha R., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - LePaw, Sylvia, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lenz, Edward, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Leung, Kok-Ming, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Levi, Enrico, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Levine, Nathan, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Levitt, Ian, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Levon, Kalle, 1997, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Levy, Joel H., undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Levy, Leon, 1992, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Levy, Stephen, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Lewin, Menachem, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Lewis, James P., undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Lewis, Robert E., 1960, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Li, Joan, circa 1996 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lian, Kenneth, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Libby, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Liccardi, Anthony, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Lieber, Art, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Lieberman, Burton, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Likel, Harry C., undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Likourezos, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Lin, Feng-Bao, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lin, Li-Chieh, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Lindenauer, Abraham, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Lindholm, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Lindsay, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Link, O. Winston, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Link, O. Winston -- Photos by, undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Linton, Jonathan D., undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Linza, Stuart, undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Lipitz, Elliott A., undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Lippman, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Litt, Benjamin, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Littlejohn, Lomax, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Liwschitz-Garik [?], 1942 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Lobenberg, Michel, undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Loebl, Ernest M., undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lombarden, undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Lombardino, Joseph G., undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lombardo, George A., undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Lord, Thomas, circa 1987 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Lorenz, Patricia A., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Low, Seth, circa 1866 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Lowe, Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Lowe, Helen, undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Lu, I-Tai, undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Lubell, Peter, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Luna, Anthony, undated (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Lundberg, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Luntey, Eugene H., undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Lurie, Harold, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Lutwak, Erwin, undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Lutwick, Larry, undated (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Lybeck, Al, undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Lynch, James E., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Lynch, Patrick "Pat", undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Lynch, William A., undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Lynford, Jeffrey, undated (Box 5, Folder 114)
- M
  - MacDiarmid, Alan G., undated (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - MacDonald, Kathleen, undated (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - MacDuff, John N., undated (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Maciag, Robert J., 1986, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Mack, Edward, circa 1905 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - MacKenzie, Lt. Col. F., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Maggio, Edward, undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Maillacheruvu, Krishnanand Y. "Kris", undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Mainiero, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Malament, undated (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Maloof, Roula, undated (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Mancuso, Michael Jr., undated (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Mandelbaum, Richard, circa 1993 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Mandl, undated (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Manniello, John B. Louis, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Mansfield, Joseph, circa 1964 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Marchesi, W., undated (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Marchi, undated (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Marcus, Rudolph A., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Marcuvitz, Nathan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Marder, Arnold R., 1974, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Mardus, Fred and Edna, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Margolin, Harold, undated (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Mark, Hans, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Mark, Herman: See Herman Mark Collection, undated
  - Markowitz, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Marks, James "Buck", circa 1996 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Marks, Leonard, undated (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Marks, Sylvia K., undated (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Marschhausen, George W., undated (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Marshall, Gillian P., undated (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Marshall, John F., undated (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Martcheva, Maia, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Martin, Harold E., undated (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Martinez, Arthur C., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Martini, Joseph, undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Martinovich, Betty, undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Martucci, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Mason, Roger, undated (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Masaryk, Jan, 0194-1941 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Masselos, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Massey, Walter E., 2000 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Mastronardi, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Matalon, Moshe, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Match, Robert K., undated (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Matsuoka, Shiro, undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Matthews, Craig C., undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Mattiello, Joseph J., undated (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - May, William F., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Mayo, John S., undated (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Mazziota, Daniel, undated (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Mazzucco, Salvatore, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - McCabe, Warren L., 1950, 1954, 1955, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - McCauley [?], undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - McDonald, undated (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - McDonald, JoAnn, undated (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - McGinnis, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - McIlveen, Edward E., undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - McKeen, John E., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - McLaughlin, Patricia A., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - McLean, Noel, undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - McNear, Cheryl, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - McShane, William, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Mead, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Meglino, Bruce M., undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Meinhold, Artie, 1942, 1950, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Meinhold, Herbert, undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Meites, Lou, undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Memon, Nasir, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Menashe, Louis, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Mendik, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Mermelstein, David, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Mesrobian, Robert B., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Messerschmitt, Richard, circa 1996 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Messina, Philip, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Meyer, Leonard S., undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Meyers, Bernard L., undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Michels, Frank G., undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Middendorf, Henry Q., 1956, 1967, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Midgette, Ernst L., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Mijovic, Jovan, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Milas, Alfred, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Milgram, Joseph B. Jr., undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Edward, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Irving F., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miller, J., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Wharton, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miller, William T., undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Millet, Marcus J., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mishkin, E., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mishuck, Eli, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Misra, Asoka, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mitnitsky, Samuel, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Molof, Alan H., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mones, Arthur H., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Montrone, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Moore, George E., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Robert J., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Morancie, Horace L., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Morawetz, Herbert, 1978, 1981, 1995, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Morduchow, Morris, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Philip, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Morrison, Alexander W., undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Moslon, Julie, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Motzkin, Shirley, 1971, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Mow, William C. W., undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Moy, Kirsten S., undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Mueller, Wheeler, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Mugglin, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mukherjee, Kalinath, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mukhopadhay, Sharmila M., undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mulcahy, David F., undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mulkin, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Muller, F., undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Muller, S. H., undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Murawski, Thomas, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Murphy, Donald, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Murray, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Murray, Robt T.K., undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Murray, R. William, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Muss, Jonathan, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Myers, Robert J., undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Myerson, Allan, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- N
  - Nader, Ralph, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Nadro, Edward Jr., undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Naevestad, Roy, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Nagler, Stewart G., 1985, 1993, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nagy, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Nakahara, Tsuneo, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Napoli, Rudolph P., undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Naumovich, Gleb, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Nelson, Ed, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Nelson, Richard E., undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Nelson, Theodore W., circa 1978 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Nespoli, Paolo A., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Neugebauer, George H., undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Newman, Joseph H., undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Newstein, Maurice C., undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Newton, Harry, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nickelson, Stanley, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Nicks, Oran W., undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Nielsen, John P., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Nies, Nelson, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Nijhawan, Ramesh K., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Nisenson, Stan, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Noetzel, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Nomovetsky, Frederick, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Nones, Allan S., undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Norton, Richard A., Col., undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Nourbakhsh, Said, 1986, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Novomestky, Frederick, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Nowak, Theodore, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Nulty, Thomas, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Nummy, W.R., undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Nyquist, Ewald B., undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
- O
  - Obeid, Diya, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Obermeyer, Charles, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - O'Connell. Liam P.F., circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - O'Connor, Arthur M., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - O'Connor, John J., 1954, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - O'Dea, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Oergel, Charles T., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Oguchi, Bunichi, circa 1996 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Okamoto, Yoshiyuki, undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - O'Leary, Hazel R., undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Oleck, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Olexson, Gerard, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Oliner, Arthur A., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Olpin, A.R., undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Olsen, John C., circa 1937, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Olshan, Kenneth S., 1990s (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Omoagbi, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Ooro, Otieno, undated (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Oppenheim, Alan and Rosa, circa 1998 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Orden, C.J., undated (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - O'Rourke, Kevin, undated (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Orso, Camillo A., circa 1997 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Osborne, undated (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Oster, Gerald, undated (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Othmer, Donald, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Othmer, Mildred Topp, undated (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Otugen, M. Volkan, undated (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Oussani, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Overberger, Charles G., 1952, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Overstreet, Jamahl W., undated (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Owades, Joseph L., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Owens, Major, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Oxman, Jack, undated (Box 6, Folder 110)
- P
  - Pace, Norma, undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Pack, Arthur, undated (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Packard, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Paczkowski, Henry C., undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Padavan, Frank, undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Padro, Dianne, undated (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Paige, Clifford E., undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Palchefsky, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Pallo, Joseph S., undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Palmer, Charles, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Palocz, Istvan, circa 1987 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Pannaparayil, Thomas, undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Panwar, Shivendra, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Panzer, Marvin, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Papoulis, Athanasios, undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Parandelis, Raina, undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Parikh, Mihir, undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Park, Lawrence, undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Parker, Jack R., undated (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Parker, John C., undated (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Parry, John P., undated (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Parsons, Laura, undated (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Parsons, Richard D., undated (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Pascal, Donald D., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Patel, Rutton D., undated (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Patterson, Zahra, undated (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Pauling, Linus, undated (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Peale, Mundy I., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Pearce, Eli, 1974, 1986, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Pearlstein, Morton, undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Peck, Nicole, undated (Box 6, Folder 141)